<motd version="171" lastChanged="2015-09-16 19:06:06">Welcome to the Mr. Green MTA Race server!&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A; ________ About us _________&#x0D;&#x0A;We also have a MTA Mix mode vehicle server. Press F2 twice to switch to it.&#x0A;&#x0A;This is a racing server. Follow the checkpoints untill the finish. After the first finish there are 45 seconds before the map will end. Press enter to respawn.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;Press F6 to setup Green-Coins, they can be earned on all Mr. Green servers. On this server you earn Green-Coins by winning maps, earning achievements or setting new tops.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;_____Recent changes_____&#x0A;* Event server at party.mrgreengaming.com !&#x0A;Type /party to join&#x0A;&#x0A;* 16-09-2015&#x0A;Double GC active!&#x0A;&#x0A;* 14-09-2015&#x0A;Wednesday is Mr Green&apos;s 9th anniversary!&#x0A;For the whole day there will be double gc rewards.&#x0A;From 7pm CEST there will also be an event server where we play fun mta modes with the whole community, come and join!&#x0A;&#x0A;* 05-09-2015&#x0A;F1madkiller is the new admin and Cena is our new mix mapmanager!&#x0A;Also new maps should be uploaded here from now on: http://mrgreengaming.com/mta/. &#x0A;- SDK&#x0A;&#x0A;* 27-08-2015&#x0A;We had a server crash and had to restart from a backup. Most of the data is restored but some stuff might be lost (nothing gc related luckily)&#x0A;- SDK&#x0A;&#x0A;* 30-07-2015&#x0A; New admin AleksCore and new uploader for race,&#x0A;Bob_Taylor! -SDK&#x0A;&#x0A;* 28-07-2015&#x0A;You now keep your playtime after reconnecting or switching to the other server! -SDK&#x0A;&#x0A;* 15-07-2015&#x0A;New /blocker command for mods&#x0A;http://mrgreengaming.com/forums/topic/16479-moderators-with-blocker/&#x0A;/deletedmaps to see what maps were deleted recently&#x0A;&#x0A;* 11-07-2015&#x0A;Winners now get a discount to 350 GC on their next map purchase&#x0A;-SDK&#x0A;&#x0A;* 07-07*2015&#x0A;New map price and modes can&apos;t be skipped anymore!&#x0A;-SDK&#x0A;&#x0A;* 05-07-2015&#x0A;New admin Jack123! /votekut&#x0A;&#x0A;* 02-02-2015&#x0A;New sidebar added, press G to open.&#x0A;&#x0A;* 02-02-2015&#x0A;Welcome to two new admins, besweeet and Cena!&#x0A;If you are aplying for admin, there are new rules, check the forum for details.&#x0A;&#x0A;* (23-10-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;- New Help Menu added (f9)&#x0D;&#x0A;- New Settings Menu added (/settings)  -Kali&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;* (22-10-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;6 New horns added to the gcshop  -Kali&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(12-10-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;Added chrome wheels to /settings - kali&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A; *(08-10-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;New horns on the GC Shop! (F6) More comming soon&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(20-09-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;GCshop temporarily disabled due server issues&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;* (12-09-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;New hud, learn to love it or disable it with /hud 0 or and /sradar 0, alternative is  /sphud 1&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;* (08-09-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;New map rules are in effect from now on, check them on the forum!&#x0D;&#x0A;Also the map queue got nerfed, you can use /fpslimit now and rhino is removed from NTS.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(18-08-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;Language chat is disabled, will be back soon(ish)&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(17-08-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;Language Chat added, Press F10 to set your settings and read the help page. Remember that only English is allowed in the main chat from now on! - Kali&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(17-08-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;InterChat (Chat between race and mix)  is now bound the the key &quot;U&quot; instead of having to write &quot;+&quot; - Kali&#x0D;&#x0A;.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(15-08-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;warp. is now uploading your contributions to our servers, please don&apos;t ask him to upload your maps. (Unless you have tacos)&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(03-08-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;Fresh admins!&#x0D;&#x0A;http://mrgreengaming.com/forums/topic/14555-new-admins-retard-and-bob-taylor&#x0D;&#x0A;*(31-07-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;MTA 1.4 is now released! More info @&#x0D;&#x0A;http://mrgreengaming.com/forums/topic/14525-multi-theft-auto-san-andreas-14-released/&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(21-07-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;http://mrgreengaming.com/forums/topic/14450-gc-purchases-are-now-restored&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(20-07-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;The GC backup from July 2013 is now activated. Tomorrow we will restore the GC from purchases from the past year. Accounts that were made after the backup are lost unfortunately.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(17-07-2014)&#x0D;&#x0A;Our forum is now restored, you can check the current status of Mr.Green at&#x0D;&#x0A;https://mrgreengaming.com/forums/topic/14407-future-of-mr-green/    -warp.&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(10-07-2014) New update on the GC issue can be found here: http://forums.mrgreengaming.com/tmp/topic/1-shit-hit-the-fan/?p=489   -Kali&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(29-06-2014) GC can be collected again temporary and will be stored on your serial. You can not do anything with it yet though -SDK&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(28-06-2014) Due technical problems everything related with greencoins isn&apos;t available at the moment. More information is available at our forum. &#x0D;&#x0A;( http://forums.mrgreengaming.com/tmp/topic/1-shit-hit-the-fan/ )&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(26-01-2014) The league signups have been closed. Good luck to the racers!&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;*(25-01-2014) Last day to sign up for the Mr. Green Racing League, win a lot of greencoins!&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;* (15-01-2014) Mr. Green Racing League announced! If you want to participate, check the forum! http://forums.mrgreengaming.com/topic/15878-mr-green-racing-league-announcement/&#x0D;&#x0A;&#x0D;&#x0A;* (13-01-2014) New custom horns have been added to the server!&#x0;</motd>
