<help>
-------------------------------------
--- Full Command list for players ---
-------------------------------------

/rules                       - Displays the server rules
/admins                      - Shows the current online admins
/report                      - Report someone/something to the admins
/motd                        - Displays the Server MOTD (Message Of The Day) . Here's where we usually announce updates.
/upload                      - URL to upload maps
/irc                         - IRC info
/lol                         - l.o.l.
/song                        - Shows the directory of the currently playing song
/players mix                 - Lookup how many and who's playing on the mix server

/kill                        - Get a Hunter, Hydra or Rhino
/spec /spectate[name]        - Go to spectator (press b) , or spectate a specific player 

/country [name]              - Checks country of a player
/seen [fullName]             - Displays last seen date and time of your friends in GMT time
/getvehid                    - Check what vehicle you're driving
/stats [name]                - Check stats of a player (F10)

/like /dislike               - Adds a like/dislike to the current map
/mapinfo [map]               - Show mapinfo (Map creator, description, likes, dislikes, last time played, your own personal best time)
/maps                        - List of the maps we have (in console = F8)
/gamemodes                   - List of modes and how many maps we have (in console = F8)
/checkmap [map]              - Check if a certain map is online
/nextmap                     - Check what the next map is

/soundsoff /soundson         - Disables/enables all map songs and custom horns sounds
/soundvolume [%]             - Set the race voices to a lower volume
/mode [mph/kmh/none]         - Changes the speed-o-meter's functionality. Can also disable it with 'none'
/oldcam                      - Changes between bumper camera mode and cockpit camera mode
/toggleicon                  - Toggle the icon above a player when he's typing
/resizeicon [%]              - Resize it to a percentage
/seticonvis [%]              - Add alpha to the icon
/hidenext                    - Hide the nextmap window
/hidemsg                     - Hide the floating game messages
/cpdelays                    - Toggle or hide the checkpoint splittime indicator
/setdelaypos [x y]           - Move the split indicator (range 0 to 1)
/progress                    - Show the progress bar (F7, hold for settings)
/board                       - Shows a smaller version of a rank board
/sphud                       - Show a different version of the race HUD
/showtimes                   - Shows the toptimes for the current map (F5)
/showsensor                  - Toggle the traffic sensor (F4)
/scoreboard                  - Show the scoreboard (tab)
/fpslimit [lim]              - Set your own fps limit

/settings                    - Displays the Shader Menu. You can add ENB Series to MTA! But beware of the unstability!
/radio                       - Displays a window where you can load your own Stream URLs and listen to them (i.e broadcast radio)

/gclogin [email] [password]  - Logs you into GreenCoins. (More information: F6). Note that if you should need to change your pass you can just change your Forum password. 
/gclogout                    - Logs you out of GreenCoins
/gc                          - Toggles your GreenCoins counter
/greencoins [name]           - Request the total and session GreenCoins of a player

/gcshop (F6)                 - The shop!
(most of the next gc commands you'll never use because they're already inside the gcshop gui)
/gcflipv2 (1)                - The command linked to button 1 used to turn over your vehicle
/gcburnv2 (2)                - The command linked to button 2 used to add some burn time before exploding
/gcspawn  (3)                - The command linked to button 3 used to change your spawnpoint
/gcbuyveh [id]               - Buys a vehicle so you can mod it
/gcsetmod [id] [type] ...    - Add's a mod to a specific vehicle you bought [types: upgrade, remupgrade, paintjob, vcolor2 (RGB color), lcolor (RGB lights), neon]

/locknick                    - If you're logged into GCs, this command will lock your nick to your account. So a login is required each time the nick is used
/unlocknick                  - If the nick was previously locked, it unlocks it.
/register /login /logout     - Old mta system, we use greencoin logins, so no need to use this anymore

/bind [key] [command] [arg]  - Binds a command to a key of your choice. Example: /bind f1 gclogin MyUser MyPassword -> This will make f1 your login button!
/pm /msg [fullName] [text]   - Sends a private message to a specific player. An alternative to this is F3!


---Keys available---
F1            - Player Achievements! You can view your own achievements and other player's with F1.
F2            - Go to the mix server
F3            - Mr. Green chat. (private chat where you can speak to any player in the server)
F4            - Toggles traffic arrows
F5            - Shows top times of current map
F6            - Toggles the GreenCoins Shop Main Menu 
F7            - Toggles the race progress bar (right side player positions)
F8            - Toggles the MTA Client Console
F9            - Toggles this Help Menu
F10           - Toggles Player Stats (your own)    
F11           - Toggle the radar
F12           - Take a screenshot
Enter         - Kills yourself
Tab           - Displays the scoreboard. 
Z             - Voice Chat. Can only be used once the feature has been bought from the GC Shop (F6)    
LCtrl         - Makes your bike jump if held a few seconds and then released    

--IRC Help---
Mr. Green has its own IRC channels. You can ask for an admin or you can simply find help at: 
server: irc.gtanet.com 
main channel: #mrgreen
mta echo channel: #mrgreen.mta
The MTA echo channel supports commands. MrGreenMTA is the bot that handles them. Type !commands upon join to learn more about them
</help>